in this code
our numbers hash was not mutated
because the select method is not a
destructive method
instead it returns a new hash
which we can see by outputting the low
numbers hash on line 11
and our original hash numbers on line
12.
you can see by our second line of output
that invoking the hash select method
on numbers did not mutate the hash
instead we assigned the newly returned
hash
to the variable low numbers seen on line
1 of this output
now we need to modify this code to use
the destructive version of select
and that is select with the bang
operator
now when we output low numbers on line
and numbers on line 12 we expect to see
the same hash
and we do you can see that we
destructively modified the numbers hash
numbers and low numbers are not two
different hashes with the same key value
pairs
they are actually two different
variables referencing the same exact
hash and that's because
the destructive select returns the
mutated hash it made sense to
assign the return value of the
non-destructive select
to a variable low numbers so that we
could pass it around and use it in our
code
when we modify this hash destructively
using the destructive select
we can pass around that mutated hash
with the numbers variable
so we don't necessarily need to assign
the return value of this
destructive call to select to a new
variable
you